# **AKIF SAHIN** KORKMAZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### **PROGRAMMING** LANGUAGES

experience

Python

JavaScript / TypeScript

Has a lot of experience

Html 5 / Css 3

(Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind Css etc.)

Has experience and exposure

SQL + MongoDB

Has exposure but

not much experience

R

### **ACCOUNTS**



https://www.linkedin.com/in/akifsahin-korkmaz



https://github.com/akifsahinkorkmaz Check my projects!

## CONTACT ME

(+90) 5418223889 akifsahinkorkmaz@outlook.com

Gokcek district, 359. street, 11. apartment, door 6, Sincan province Ankara/Turkey

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have had great interest in programming and finance for many years. I have experience with most-used stacks for full-stack web development and data engineering. I am a good team player with excellent verbal and written communicational skills and a dedicated/fast learner.

#### PROGRAMMING SKILLSET

- Python
  - o Web:
    - Django / Flask
    - Requests / Selenium
    - Keyboard / Pyautogui
  - o Data/others:
    - Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib
    - TensorFlow, PyTorch
    - SQLite, Openpyxl, yfinance etc.
    - PIL, Scikit-Image, Pgmagick
- · Javascript / Typescript
  - Web (Backend):
    - Express JS / Nest JS
    - Mongoose / Sequelize
  - o Web (Frontend):
    - React (+ React Native)
    - Framer Motion (for React)
    - Svelte
    - Angular
    - Peer.is

Other technologies i have experience with:

- Github
- Docker
- AWS
- MongoDB Atlas
- Linux
- Nginx
- Gunicorn
- TCP, UDP, RTC, HTTP and Socket protocols
- · Conventional payment gateways
- · Crypto payment gateways

### WORK EXPERIENCE / ACHIEVEMENTS

Freelance full stack web development [2021-2022]:

Data engineering and visualisation for scientific and commercial researchs [2020-2022]

Entrepreneurship:

- NFT promoting web app (NFT-Announcer) [2021-2022]
- Gazi University Technology Office entrepreneurship/IT education programme. [2020-2021]
- U4S entrepreneurship programme winner of Ankara with a micromobility project. [2020-2021]

Others:

• Shadow writing (English and Turkish) [2019-2020]

#### **EDUCATION**

Hacettepe University - Mining Engineering | 2022-Present

• English Proficiency Test (Advanced)

Asfa Science High School | 2014-2018

- 1st place with accessibility project at Lego League in Ankara.
- Participated at national science competitions (TUBITAK).

(Ankara University - Veterinary Faculty | 2018-2022)

#### OTHER SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS

**LANGUAGES** 

· UI design with Figma, AdobeXD and Canva

· API testing with Insomnia

- · Image manipulation (intermediate level)
- SVG art & design
- Financial literacy certificate
- · Driver's License

Turkish (Native) English (Advanced)